[Music]
[音乐]
this is nick with logosbynick.com and in
我是来自logosbynick.com的尼克
this tutorial i'll be demonstrating how
在本教程中，我将演示
you can create these isometric
您可以创建这些等轴测
illustrations
插图
using inkscape and this is a topic that
使用Inkscape，这是一个
i've gone over in the past however
然而，我已经过去了
thanks to some of the newer features in
中的一些新功能。
inkscape version 1.0
Inkscape 1.0版
it now makes it easier to make your
现在可以更轻松地让您的
designs have rounded corners
设计有圆角
as you can see in my example design here
正如您在我的示例设计中所看到的那样
so that is one of the things i will be
所以这是我会做的一件事
going over in this tutorial
在本教程中介绍
but before we get started if you'd like
但在我们开始之前，如果你愿意
to learn more about how inkscape works
要详细了解Inkscape的工作原理，请执行以下操作
be sure to check out my inkscape master
一定要看看我的Inkscape大师
class
班级
it's a collection of over 60 videos
这是60多个视频的集合
where i go over every tool and feature
在那里我检查了每一个工具和功能
in inkscape and i explain what it is and
在Inkscape中，我解释了它是什么
demonstrate how it works
演示其工作原理
i'll have a link in the description of
我会在描述中有一个链接
the video if you want to check that out
这个视频如果你想看看的话
so the first thing we want to do when we
所以我们要做的第一件事就是
have inkscape open here is set up our
在此处打开Inkscape将设置我们的
document so that we are all working with
文档，以便我们所有人都使用
a similar view and layout so i'll come
相似的视野和布局，所以我会来的
over here to where it says
从这里到上面写着
view make sure we have custom selected
查看确保我们已自定义选择
come up here to where it says zoom i'm
到这里来，上面写着，我在
going to zoom in at one to one
以1比1的比例放大
you're going to want to make sure you
你会希望确保你
have snapping enabled up here it should
在这里启用捕捉应该是
be enabled by default but just make sure
默认情况下启用，但只需确保
it's enabled
它已启用
and the snapping we want over here is
我们在这里想要的快照是
snap to cusp nodes
捕捉到尖点节点
and then snap to grids which is over
然后捕捉到已结束的栅格
here very important for this to be
这一点非常重要
enabled
启用
so what i'm going to do now is set up
所以我现在要做的就是设置
the isometric grid on the canvas i'll
画布上的等轴测网格我将
come over here where it says file
到这里来，上面写着文件
go to document properties first i just
先转到文档属性，我只是
want to get rid of the page border i'm
我想去掉页面边框，我是
going to click on this box right here
要点击这里的这个框
that says show page border to get that
上面写着显示页面边框以获取该内容
out of the way when we're trying to
别挡道，当我们试图
create our designs
创造我们的设计
and over here where it says grids let's
在这里，它写着网格，让我们
click on that tab i'm going to choose
点击我要选择的选项卡
axonometric grid
轴测网格
click new and for the grid units i'm
单击新建，然后单击我的格网单位
going to choose pixels
将选择像素
and if you notice we now have an
如果你注意到我们现在有一个
isometric grid on the canvas here i just
画布上的等轴测网格我只是
want to make those lines a little more
我想把这些台词做得更多一点
spaced out because there's too many of
因为有太多的
them
他们
on the canvas as it is so where it says
在画布上，就像它说的那样
spacing y
间距y
i'm just going to change that to 50 hit
我要把它改成50次点击
enter there we go that's a good that's a
进入那里，我们走，这很好，这是一
good happy medium right there so i'll go
好的，好的，就在那里，所以我要走了
ahead and close out of that
向前和向外靠拢
and when i'm drawing isometric designs
当我在画等轴测设计时
what i like to do is i like to start
我喜欢做的是，我喜欢从
with the smallest objects first and then
首先是最小的物体，然后是
draw outwards to the largest objects
向外画到最大的物体
that way i can ensure that i don't run
这样我就能确保我不会跑
out of boxes as i'm drawing
当我在画的时候，从盒子里拿出来
objects so what i want to do now is draw
对象，所以我现在要做的是绘制
the buttons of the phone first because
先按下电话的按键，因为
those are the smallest objects
那些是最小的物体
what i'm going to be drawing is a a
我要画的是一个
phone laying flat on a surface
手机平放在地面上
like that so let me grab
就像这样，所以让我抓起
let me grab the bezier pen which is over
我去拿那支贝塞尔笔，它已经结束了
here
这里
and if you notice the way the grid works
如果你注意到网格的工作方式
is every five lines you have a main line
是不是每五条线路就有一条主线
which is slightly darker than the other
哪一个比另一个稍微暗一些
five lines so what i'd like to do is i
五行，所以我想要做的是
like to start at one of the main lines
我想从一条主线开始
right here
就在这里
click to create a point bring the line
单击以创建点，将线
to the other main line right here
另一条主线就在这里
and over here then up back up here and
在这里，然后回到这里，然后回到这里
then back to the starting point
然后回到起点
and this is going to be the home button
这将是主页按钮
of the phone and this button is going to
这个按键将会
have rounded corners but i'm going to go
有圆角，但我要走了
back and add that later i'm going to
返回并添加这一点，稍后我将
draw everything with sharp corners first
先用锐角画出所有东西
and then i'm going to go back and make
然后我要回去做
the corners rounded later so the next
转角后来变圆了，所以第二个
biggest object for me to draw would be
我画的最大的对象将是
the screen so
屏幕是这样的
let me start out here the screen is
让我从这里开始，屏幕是
going to be over here represented by
在这里代表的是
this area
这一地区
so i'm going to start five units away
所以我要从五个单位开始
from the button on the left side and one
从左边的按钮和一个
unit up
单元启动
like that and bring it the same distance
像这样，把它带到相同的距离
to the other side
到另一边
using the main lines as a reference
以主线为参照
and then i'm going to bring this out
然后我要把这个拿出来
here
这里
one two three four now you know what i
一、二、三、四，现在你知道我
missed that let me undo that by hitting
错过了，让我用击球来撤销它
ctrl z
Ctrl z键
there we go it's pretty common to miss
我们走吧，错过是很常见的
the line you're going for so uh if you
你想要的那条线，所以，如果你
if you end up missing the line just hit
如果你最后错过了这条线，那就来吧
ctrl z to undo it
按Ctrl z键撤消该操作
or you can go back and edit it with the
或者，您可以返回并使用
nodes tool which i'll show you in a
节点工具，我将在
minute so
分钟，所以
let me bring this out here out here
让我把这个带到外面来
about that much
差不多有那么多
up here and then back to the starting
在这里，然后回到起点
point
点
now if you notice i totally missed the
现在如果你注意到我完全错过了
mark there this line is not parallel to
在那里标出这条线与之不平行
this line right here so i'm going to
这条线就在这里，所以我要
grab the nodes tool and fix that i'm
抓起节点工具并修复我的
just going to put that back over here
我要把它放回这里
where it should be
它应该在哪里
looks like i missed it by one let me try
看起来我差一分就错过了，让我试试
that
那
to move around i'm just holding ctrl and
要四处走动，我只需按住Ctrl键并
rolling up and down the mouse wheel and
上下滚动鼠标滚轮和
then i'm pressing down the mouse wheel
然后我按下鼠标滚轮
and moving mouse
和移动鼠标
to to to move around like that looks
像这样四处走动看起来
like i got to go one more like that
就像我还得再来一次一样
there we go that looks that looks right
我们走吧，看起来是对的
so what i'm going to do now is
所以我现在要做的是
create the other button up top here or
在上面创建另一个按钮，或者
actually the speaker the speaker hole
实际上演讲者就是演讲者的洞穴
i'm just going to use this
我只想用这个
duplicate this object so let me grab the
复制这个对象，让我抓取
select tool click on this object
选择工具在此对象上单击
press ctrl d to duplicate it and then
按Ctrl d复制它，然后
click and drag this
单击并拖动此选项
up here right there
就在这里，就在那里
so what i'm going to draw now is the
所以我现在要画的是
outside edge of the phone so let me go
电话的边缘，所以让我走吧
back to the bezier pen
回到贝塞尔笔下
and i'm going to start this one unit
我将启动这一个单元
away one unit away from the button here
离开这里的按钮一个单位
and then down here
然后在这下面
bring this out to about there that's
把这个拿出来，那就是
looking good
看起来不错
out here
在这里
and bring this one unit away from this
把这一个单位从这里带走
edge right here
边缘就在这里
and then back to the starting point now
然后回到现在的起点
i totally missed the mark there so let
我完全错过了目标，所以让我们
me go back and edit that
我回去编辑一下
let me grab the nodes tool this needs to
让我来获取此操作所需的节点工具
be
BE
this needs to be right here okay that's
它需要放在这里，好的，这是
looking good
看起来不错
all right so what i'm going to do now is
好了，我现在要做的是
i'm going to start rounding some of
我要开始收集一些
these corners let me go to the select
这些角落让我去精选
tool
工具
i'm going to start with the button right
我要从正确的按钮开始
here i'm going to click on that and i
在这里，我要点击它，我
want to open up the path effects menu
我想打开路径效果菜单
i'll go to path path effects
我将转到路径路径效果
and i'm going to click to add a new path
我要单击以添加一条新路径
effect this little plus button right
将这个小加号按钮放在右边
here
这里
and i'm going to look for corners if you
我要去找角落，如果你
can see i already have it typed in
我已经把它打进去了
because i was using this previously you
因为我之前用的是这个你
just type in corners
只需在角落里打字
if you remove the search function the
如果删除搜索功能，
search text it shows you all of the path
搜索文本它会向您显示所有路径
effects
效果
if you just type in corners there you go
如果你只需在角落里打字，你就可以了
there's the path effect we're looking
这是我们正在寻找的路径效应
for the corners
为角落而战
fillet chamfer there we go
菲力倒角，我们来了
and what that's going to do is let me
接下来要做的就是让我
zoom in on this if we grab the nodes
如果我们抓取节点，请放大此图
tool
工具
you notice we have these four green
你注意到我们有这四个绿色的
knots in the corners here
在这里的角落里打结
and you could take these knots and use
你可以用这些结
it to round to the corners like that
像这样绕到角落里是不可能的
i don't just want to round to that one
我不只是想绕到那个
corner though i want to round all of
虽然我想把所有的角都绕过去
these corners so i'm going to click and
这些角，所以我要点击并
drag over all four of those knots
拖到所有四个结上
and then just click in oops click and
然后只需在OOPS中点击并点击
drag this in like this to make these
把这个像这样拖进去做这些
rounded
舍入
and it looks like the snapping is
看起来这张照片是
getting in the way so i'm going to
挡道了，所以我要
temporarily disable snapping
暂时禁用捕捉
and then move this in like that
然后像这样把这个搬进来
and now i can turn snapping back on you
现在我可以转身对你发火了
know i'm going to leave it off because
我知道我会把它关掉，因为
we have to do the same thing to the
我们必须对
other buttons so
其他按钮，因此
let me come back out here and do the
让我回到这里来做
same thing to this speaker hole right
对这个音箱洞也是一样的
here
这里
add a path effect corners
添加路径效果角
click and drag over all four points and
在所有四个点上单击并拖动
then just click and drag it inward like
然后只需点击并向内拖动它，就像
that to give it rounded corners
为了让它有圆角
over here there's four different
在这里有四种不同的
settings this is the fillet setting if
设置在以下情况下这是圆角设置
you choose like chamfer it's going to
你选择像倒角一样它将会
give you a different style of corner if
给你一个不同风格的角落，如果
you're getting this different style of
你会得到这种不同风格的
corner when you do this just make sure
当你这样做的时候，只要确保
you have fillet selected
您已选择圆角
it should be there by default but maybe
默认情况下，它应该在那里，但可能
maybe it's not so that's how you can set
也许不是这样的，所以你可以这样设置
it back
它回来了
if that's the case and now i want to
如果是这样的话，现在我想
round the corners of the phone edge here
绕过手机边缘的一角
so to do that let me select that object
为此，让我选择该对象
add a new path effect corners and for
添加新的路径效果角和For
this one i want to turn snapping back on
这个，我想打开捕捉功能
because i want to snap to one of these
因为我想拍下其中一张
grid lines i'm going to click and drag
我要单击并拖动的网格线
this down
把这个放下来
or you know what i have to select all
或者你知道我必须选择所有
four of them let me click and drag over
其中四个让我可以点击并拖动
all four of them
他们四个都是
bring that in like that there we go
像这样把它拿进来，我们走
that's looking pretty good now that's
现在看起来很不错，这是
looking more like a phone
看起来更像一部手机
okay so let me uh let me go back to the
好的，那么让我，呃，让我回到
select tool
选择工具
let's select over all of these objects
让我们选择所有这些对象
and convert them to paths we'll go to
并将它们转换为我们要访问的路径
path
路径
object to path and that's going to
对象到路径，这将是
change that from a path effect to now
将其从路径效果更改为现在
it's an actual
这是一个真实的
it's an actual path not just a path
这是一条真正的道路，而不仅仅是一条道路
effect if that makes any sense
如果这有任何意义的话会有影响
the reason why i do that is because this
我这么做的原因是因为
is this is sort of a new path effect and
这是一种新的路径效应
it doesn't really
这并不是真的
function uh the way it should sometimes
功能，呃，有时应该是这样的
i'll there's sometimes i'm working with
我有时会和我一起工作
this path effect and like the corners
这种路径效果和喜欢的角落
will just randomly go back to being
将会随机地恢复为
sharp
锐利
and i'll have to go back and make them
我将不得不回去制作它们
rounded again that's why i like to
再四舍五入，这就是为什么我喜欢
convert them to path beforehand so i
提前将它们转换为路径，以便我
don't have to go back and do that so
不用再回去了，那样做
let me now let's now take the button
现在让我来，让我们来按下按钮
here and just raise that to the top with
在这里，只要把它举到上面就可以了
this button over here race
这里的这个按钮在比赛
race selection to the top same thing
种族选择达到顶端相同的事情
with the screen right here raise
随着屏幕在这里升起
selection to the top
选择到最上面
nothing visually is happening on the
在视觉上没有发生任何事情
screen as you do this we're just doing
当你这样做的时候，我们只是在做
this so that
这样做是为了
we have these objects layered above the
我们将这些对象放置在
background which is the phone
背景是哪部手机
edge here and i'll do the same thing to
这里的边缘，我会做同样的事情
this raise this to the top
这把这个升到了顶端
and now i want to fill this in with some
现在我想在这里面填上一些
color so i'm going to take this object
颜色，所以我要把这个物体
right here
就在这里
and let's open up the fill and stroke
让我们打开填充物和笔触
menu with this button over here
这里有这个按钮的菜单
or you can press ctrl shift and f on the
或者，您可以按Ctrl Shift和
keyboard
键盘
and i'm going to fill this in maybe with
我要把这个填上，也许是
like a light shade of gray like that
就像那淡淡的灰色
that's looking pretty good let's get rid
看起来不错，我们把它扔掉吧
of the outline by holding shift and
通过按住Shift和
clicking on the x over here
点击这里的x
i might actually might want to make that
我可能真的想把它做成
a little darker so i can see it better
再暗一点，这样我就能看得更清楚
and now i will do the same thing for
现在我会为你做同样的事
this button i'm going to make this maybe
我要做的这个按钮可能是
a darker shade of gray
较深的灰色
let me get rid of that outline by
让我通过以下方式去掉这个提纲
holding shift and clicking the x
按住Shift键并单击x
and i'll do the same thing over here i
我会在这里做同样的事情
want to make this the same color so i'm
我想把这个做成同样的颜色，所以我
just going to grab the dropper which is
只是去拿滴管，这是
over here and just select that
在这里，只需选择那个
so it's the same color and then get rid
所以它是同样的颜色，然后去掉
of the outline by holding shift and
通过按住Shift和
clicking the x
单击x
and now i will grab the screen and i
现在我要抓起屏幕，我
guess i will make that
我想我会做的。
i guess i'll make that white for now let
我想我现在会把它改成白色的
me get rid of the
我要除掉那些
outline by shift-clicking the x like
按住Shift键并单击类似x的轮廓
that
那
and now what i want to do is i want to
现在我想做的是我想要
give this phone a little bit of depth i
给这款手机一点深度
want to make it look like it's a
想让它看起来像是
three-dimensional object so i'm gonna
三维物体，所以我要
i'm gonna duplicate this background over
我要把这个背景复制一遍
here and move it down a little bit
在这里，把它往下移一点
so let me select the object right click
所以让我选择对象，右键单击
it and go to duplicate
它和去复制
then hold ctrl and move it down like
然后按住Ctrl键并向下移动它，如下所示
that and
这和
drop it to the bottom over here where it
把它扔到这里的底部，在那里
says lower selection to the bottom and i
表示较低的选项位于底部，而我
want to make this the same color that
我想把这个做成和那个颜色一样的
this object is over here so let me grab
这个东西在这里，让我拿一下
the dropper tool
滴管工具
click on that and there we go
点击它，我们就可以开始了
i actually might want to move this up a
实际上，我可能想把这件事提前一步
little bit i don't want that much depth
有一点，我不想要那么多深度
that looks pretty good right there so if
这看起来很不错，所以如果
you notice here
你注意到了吗？
there's an empty space between the edges
两边之间有一片空白
of these two objects right here so we
这两个物体在这里，所以我们
want to add
想要添加
lines right here to fill that in to make
就在这里填上几行来制作
it look to make it look the way it's
它看起来是为了让它看起来像是
supposed to look
应该看起来
to do that maybe i should put this down
为了做到这一点，也许我应该把这个放下
back to where it was to better
回到原来更好的地方
illustrate that
说明这一点
to better illustrate what i'm about to
为了更好地说明我接下来要说的
do so i'm going to put that back to
这样做，我要把它放回
where it was
它在哪里？
i'm going to select both objects the
我将选择这两个对象
original background i'm going to hold
我将保留原始背景
shift click the uh the new background we
按住Shift键点击我们的新背景
just created and i'll go to extensions
刚刚创建，我将转到扩展
generate from path and extrude
从路径生成并拉伸
and i want to make sure we have polygon
我想确保我们有一个多边形
selected and not lines and go ahead and
选定行，而不是行，然后继续
click apply
单击应用
and that's going to create new objects
这将创建新的对象
between the two objects we have selected
在我们选择的两个对象之间
as you can see here
正如你在这里看到的
it created all of those objects so i
它创造了所有这些物体，所以我
want to take this object that we just
想要拿到这个物体，我们刚刚
created
vbl.创建
and i want to ungroup that with this
我想用这个来解开它
button up here or ctrl shift ungroup
按下此处的按钮或按Ctrl Shift键取消分组
and i want to get rid of everything
我想扔掉所有的东西
except for these lines over
除了上面的这些线
here that we just created so i'm going
这是我们刚刚创建的，所以我要
to hold shift and click on that little
按住Shift键并单击那个小点
object right there to deselect it
对象，以取消选择它
come over here hold shift click on this
到这里来，按住Shift键，点击这个
object to deselect that
对象以取消选择该
and then press delete on the keyboard to
然后按键盘上的Delete键以
get rid of everything else
把其他东西都扔掉
and now i can take this object hold
现在我可以拿着这个物体
shift
换班
take this object and then hold shift and
获取此对象，然后按住Shift键并
take the bottom object
拿最下面的物体
and unify them all together by going to
并通过以下方式将它们统一起来
path
路径
union and as you can see now it looks
联合，正如你现在看到的，它看起来
the way it's supposed to look
它应该是什么样子的
and if you temporarily disable let me
如果你暂时停用，让我
hold shift
按住Shift键
if you hold shift and press three on the
如果按住Shift键并按下三键
keyboard it will temporarily disable
它将暂时禁用键盘
the grid on this on the screen so you
屏幕上的网格，所以你可以
can see how it looks without the grid
我可以看到没有网格是什么样子
getting in the way
挡道而行
i might want to take this screen and
我可能想拿着这个屏幕
make this darker like that there we go
让这一切变得更黑暗，我们开始了
now it's looking more like a phone
现在它看起来更像是一部手机
okay so the phone part of the design is
好的，所以设计的手机部分是
out of the way i'm now going to create
现在，我要创建一个
like a little uh
像是有点呃
like a little chat bubble to go over the
就像一个小小的聊天泡泡来回顾
uh the top of it here like i showed you
呃，就像我给你展示的那样，最上面的部分
in the
在
the design of the thumbnail to put the
缩略图的设计将
grid back to where it was
网格恢复到原来的位置
i'm just going to hold shift and press
我只需要按住Shift键并按下
three on the keyboard
键盘上的三个
or other or in other words you just use
或者其他或者换句话说，你只是用
the pound key which is
井号键，即
up here where it says view page grid
上面显示查看页面网格的位置
that's another way you can toggle that
这是你可以切换的另一种方式
off and on i just like to use the
断断续续地，我只是喜欢用
keyboard shortcut so
键盘快捷键SO
let's create a chat bubble to go over
让我们创造一个聊天泡泡来回顾一下
here now so i'm going to come over here
现在，我要走到这里来
out of the way
别挡道
i'm going to create three circles to
我要创建三个圆圈来
make it look like somebody's typing
让它看起来像是有人在打字
so let me grab the bezier pen
所以让我拿起贝塞尔钢笔
start right there again i'm using the
从那里重新开始，我正在使用
main lines in increments of five to
主线以5%至5%的增量
create these
创建这些
there we go i'm just going to duplicate
好了，我要复制一份
this
这
ctrl d move this over here so that it's
Ctrl我会把这个移到这里，这样它就
one unit apart
相隔一个单位
ctrl d so that it's one unit apart
Ctrl%d以使其相隔一个单位
and now i'm going to draw a box going
现在我要画一个方框
around these three that's two units
在这三个单元周围是两个单元
apart so let me go back to the bezier
分开，所以让我回到贝塞尔
pen
钢笔
i want to start out two units away one
我想从一个单位的两个单位开始
two
二
come up here like that one two
像这样走到这里来，一二
good over there
很好，在那里
and then back to the starting point
然后回到起点
let's see if that worked okay yeah it
让我们看看这是不是起作用了，好的，是的
looks like i got that right
看起来我猜对了
all right so now what i will do is i
好了，现在我要做的是
will round the corners of these objects
会绕过这些物体的角落
here so let me
来吧，让我来
grab the select tool let me select this
抓住选择工具，让我选择这个
object
对象
add a new path effect corners
添加新的路径效果角
go to the nodes tool select all of these
转到结点工具，选择所有这些
nodes right here
节点就在这里
and then just click and drag them in
然后只需点击并将它们拖入
like that
就像这样
let me turn off snapping so that i can
让我关闭捕捉，这样我就可以
get these a little closer to each other
把这些东西靠得更近一点
without them getting in the way
没有他们的阻挠
box over here
盒子在这里
and now what i will do is i will do the
现在我要做的是我会做
same thing to this object right here so
这个物体也是如此，所以
let me click on that
让我点击一下
add a path effect rounded
添加四舍五入的路径效果
and for this one i will turn snapping
对于这一次，我将转而抓拍
back on
重新开机
maybe right about there that looks
也许就在那里，看起来
pretty good so now i want to grab the
很好，所以现在我想抓住
select tool
选择工具
click and drag over all of these convert
在所有这些转换上单击并拖动
these to pads by going to path
这些通过PATH转到焊盘
object to path and now i'm going to
反对PATH，现在我要
create a little point down here on the
在下面的位置创建一个小点
bubble
气泡
so let me grab the bezier pen again i'm
所以让我再一次拿起贝塞尔钢笔
going to come in over here a little bit
我要到这里来一点
bring this down to about here
把这个拿到这里来
and then bring this across over here
然后把这个带到这里来
this is the only line we're drawing
这是我们唯一要画的一条线
that's not going according to the grid
这不是根据网格进行的
so i'm going to bring this up here like
所以我要把这个拿到这里来
and then back to the starting point and
然后回到起点，然后
unify those two together by holding
通过持有将这两者统一在一起
shift
换班
and clicking on the object next to it
并点击它旁边的对象
and go to path
并转到路径
union and now it's one shape like a
联合，现在它是一个形状像一个
speech bubble
言语气泡
now much like we did with the phone and
现在就像我们用电话和
the three-dimensional
三度空间
drop here i want to do the same thing
停在这里我也想做同样的事情
let me take this object first i want to
让我先拿着这个东西，我想
color this in actually
把这个涂上颜色
let's take these three circles right
让我们把这三个圆圈做对
here select those all raise those to the
在这里选择那些都将那些提升到
top
顶部
and then fill them in with white
然后用白色填充它们
nothing's going to visually change on
在视觉上不会有任何改变
the canvas because the canvas background
画布是因为画布背景
is white so you have a white object
是白色的，所以你有一个白色的物体
against a white background so it doesn't
以白色背景为背景，所以它不会
look like it's there but there is a
看起来它就在那里，但有一个
white fill there
白色填充物在那里
let me get rid of the outline by holding
让我拿着它把轮廓去掉
shift and pressing x
Shift并按x键
over here in the bottom left corner and
在这里的左下角
something like
像这样的东西
blue or green or yellow or whatever
蓝色或绿色或黄色或其他任何颜色
whatever color you want to make it
你想做什么颜色的？
i'll just use that color blue get rid of
我就用那个蓝色去掉吧
the outline
提纲
shift clicking the x and let me
按住Shift键，然后让我
duplicate this by pressing ctrl d
按Ctrld复制此命令
and i will make this one a little darker
我会把这张做得更暗一点
like that
就像这样
maybe even use an off shade of blue like
甚至可以用一种深浅不一的蓝色
that
那
bring this out here send that to the
把这个拿出来，把那个送到
bottom this button over here lower
把这颗纽扣往下压一点
selection to the bottom
选择到底部
there we go and now i want to extrude
我们开始了，现在我想要挤出
these two together so let me hold shift
这两个在一起，所以让我按住Shift
and click on both of those
然后点击这两个按钮
and go to extensions generate from path
并转到从路径生成的扩展
extrude and click apply
拉伸并单击应用
and then just give it a minute to do its
然后给它一分钟的时间来做它
thing when i was doing this tutorial
当我在做这篇教程的时候
setting it up before it took a while for
在设置它之前花了一段时间
this to
此至
load but this time it went nice and
但这一次很顺利，
quick so that's good let me close out of
快，所以这很好，让我关闭
that
那
we now have this object that we're
我们现在有了这个物体，我们是
looking for let me ungroup that with the
寻找，让我解开它与
ungroup button
取消分组按钮
and again i want to keep this object
再一次，我想保留这件物品
over here that's connecting these two
在这里，连接着这两个
points together i want to keep this
积分加在一起，我想保留这一点
object over here
对象在这里
and i want to keep this object over here
我想把这个东西放在这里
and i want to delete the rest of them so
我想把剩下的都删掉
i'll hold shift
我会轮班的
click that object to deselect it hold
单击该对象以取消选择其暂挂
shift
换班
click that object to deselect it and
单击该对象以取消选择它，然后
then come over here hold shift
然后到这里来，按住Shift
click that object deselect it and all we
单击该对象，取消选择它，然后我们所有人
have selected now are the objects we
现在选择的对象是我们
want to get rid of so now you can press
想要摆脱，所以现在你可以按
delete on the keyboard and there you go
在键盘上删除，就可以了
so let's take these objects right here
所以让我们把这些物体放在这里
that we just created shift click each of
我们刚刚创建了Shift，然后单击每个
them so we have all three selected
他们，所以我们选择了所有三个
and then hold shift and click the
然后按住Shift键并单击
original and go to path
原件并转到路径
union and that's exactly what we're
联盟，这就是我们要做的
looking for right there a three
就在那里找一个3
dimensional
维数
a 3d style isometric chat bubble
3D风格的等轴测聊天气泡
like that so what i want to do now is
像这样，所以我现在想做的是
place this over to design over the
把这个放在设计上
design so
设计这样做
i'm going to get rid of i'm going to
我要除掉我要去
temporarily get rid of the
暂时除掉
isometric grid because we don't need it
等轴测网格，因为我们不需要它
anymore we're done drawing objects so
我们不再绘制对象了，所以
let me hold shift and press three on the
让我按住Shift键并按三键
keyboard to get rid of that
用键盘来摆脱它
let me disable snapping for now so that
让我暂时禁用捕捉，以便
doesn't get in the way
不会妨碍你
click and drag over this whole thing and
在整件事上点击并拖动
press ctrl g
按Ctrl g键
on the keyboard and place it over the
在键盘上，并将其放在
object over here like that
像这样放在这里的物体
ctrl shift to scale it down and then you
按Ctrl Shift缩小比例，然后
can take this duplicate it bring it over
可以把这个复制品拿过来吗？
here
这里
and if you want you can make this a
如果你愿意，你可以把它变成
different color
不同的颜色
ungroup it i'll make this yellow
解开它，我会把它变成黄色的
make this also yellow but maybe an off
把这个也改成黄色，但可能会停下来
shade
遮阳板
maybe like red like that
也许像那样的红色
and then finally you could take this you
最后你可以拿着这个你
could put like a little drop shadow down
可以像一个小小的阴影落下
here by duplicating this object
在这里通过复制这个对象
i'm actually going to duplicate both of
我实际上要复制这两个文件
these objects the light gray hold
这些物体都是浅灰色的
shift and the dark gray ctrl d to
Shift键和深灰色Ctrl d键切换为
duplicate
复本
path union unify them together make this
路径联盟将它们统一在一起，使之成为
black
黑色
hold ctrl and just click and drag this
按住Ctrl键并单击并拖动即可
down like that send that to the bottom
像这样向下，把它送到底部
that looks pretty good and bring the
这看起来很不错，而且带来了
opacity of this down
此羽绒的不透明度
like that so we have a little bit of a
像这样，所以我们有一点
shadow there it would look a little more
阴影在那里它看起来会更多一点
convincing if this were a different
令人信服，如果这是一个不同的
color which i think i'll do that now
我想我现在要做的是什么颜色
i'll make this
我会做这个的
i'll make this something like purple
我要把这个做成紫色的。
i'll make this a lighter shade of that
我会把这个改成浅一点的
purple
紫色
and then i'll make these ones white
然后我会把这些画成白色
or you know what and i'll use the same
或者你知道吗，我会用同样的方法
shade as that purple
淡得像那紫色
and then this i'll make this a darker
然后这个我会把这个变得更暗
purple as well i'm just using the
也是紫色的，我只是在用
keyboard shortcuts to toggle back and
用于切换回和的键盘快捷键
forth between the dropper the dropper
在滴管和滴管之间向前移动
tool is
工具是
the letter d on the keyboard and the
键盘上的字母d和
select tool is s
选择工具是S
between those let me make that little
在这两者之间，让我做那一点
darker
更暗一些
that's looking good maybe add some more
看起来不错，也许再加一些
saturation to that
饱和到那个程度
that right there is what i'm looking for
就在那里，这就是我要找的
come over here make this now i can make
过来做这个，现在我可以做了
this a little darker so it's a little
这件有点暗，所以有点暗
more convincing
更有说服力
and i'd say that looks good enough so i
我会说这看起来足够好了，所以我
think that should do it for this
我觉得这样就够了
tutorial that's how you can go about
教程，这就是你可以如何去做
creating these simple
创建这些简单的
isometric drawings with rounded corners
圆角等轴测图
using some of the new features in
使用中的一些新功能
inkscape version 1.0
Inkscape 1.0版
if you have any questions leave a
如果您有任何问题，请在
comment below and as always thanks for
在下面发表评论，并一如既往地感谢
watching
观看
[Music]
[音乐]